Dramatics Files, 1878-1949
Smith College Archives
- Chapin House
  - Mar. 8, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Pride and Prejudice (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Washburn-Tenney Houses
  - May 3, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Esmerelda (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - May 24, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - A Royal Family (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Allen Recreation Field Benefit
  - Nov. 4, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - The Princess of Ming (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Wallace House
  - Nov. 22, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Miss Hobbs (Box 8, Folder 30)
- [House Dramatics]
  - [1906] (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Ham Omelet (Box 9, Folder 1)
- [House Dramatics]
  - [1906] (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The Homemade Chaperone (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - A Box of Monkeys (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Tyler House
  - Feb. 24, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Merely Mary Ann (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Lawrence House
  - Mar. 14, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - The Manoeuvres of Jane (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Morris House
  - May 5, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Little Princess (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - May 26, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Monsieur Beaucaire (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Albright House
  - Oct. 31, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Fussing in Hades (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Dec. 15, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - The Bird's Christmas Carol (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Dewey-Hatfield Houses
  - Nov. 24, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - The Shoes that Danced (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - The Little God and Dicky (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Haven-Wesley Houses
  - Mar. 2, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - The Rose and the Ring (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - Jun. 1, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - A Road to Yesterday (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Chapin House
  - Nov. 16, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Lady Bountiful (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Washburn-Tenney Houses
  - Dec.14, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 13.1-13.2)
    - You Never Can Tell (Box 9, Folder 13.1-13.2)
- Dickinson House
  - Mar. 21, 1908 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - She Stoops to Conquer (Box 9, Folder 14)
- [General - photographs] [1908] (Box 9, Folder 15)
- [House Dramatics]
  - Apr. 11, 1908 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Electra (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - May 23, 1908 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Her Great Match (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Sock and Buskin
  - Dec. 19, 1908 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - A Royal Family (Box 9, Folder 1)
- unidentified 1908-1909 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- [House Dramatics]
  - [1909] (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Maud Muller (Box 10, Folder 2)
- The Players
  - Feb. 20, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Quality Street (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Cap and Bells
  - Apr. 17, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - O My Land (Box 10, Folder 4)
- The Mummers
  - May 22, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Lady of Lyons (Box 10, Folder 5)
- The Players
  - Nov. 20, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Captain Jinks (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Cap and Bells
  - Dec. 18, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Our Mutual Friend (Box 10, Folder 7)
- French Club
  - Feb. 19, 1910 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Le Malade Imaginaire (Box 10, Folder 8)
- The Mummers
  - Mar. 12, 1910 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Men and Mice (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Sock and Buskin
  - Apr. 30, 1910 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - King Alfred's Jewels (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Latin Department
  - 1910-1911 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Rudens of Plautus (Box 11, Folder 1)
      (see Classics Department - Plays, Latin)
- Cap and Bells
  - Dec. 3, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Trelawney of the Wells (Box 11, Folder 2)
- The Mummers
  - Dec. 17, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - The Rivals (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Haven House
  - [1910] (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - (unidentified) (Box 11, Folder 4)
- German Club
  - Feb. 25, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    (see Department Clubs - German)
- Sock and Buskin
  - Mar. 11, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - The Amazons (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - Apr. 26, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - American Spirit of Today (Box 11, Folder 7)
- The Players
  - May 20, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Pot of Broth (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Albright House
  - [1911] (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - The Far Away Princess (Box 11, Folder 9)
- The Mummers
  - Nov. 25, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - You Never Can Tell (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Sock and Buskin
  - Dec. 16, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - The Progress of Mrs. Alexander (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Albright House
  - [1912] (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Pity (Box 11, Folder 12)
- The Players
  - Mar. 16, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Little Lord Fauntleroy (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Cap and Bells
  - May 4, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - The Melting Pot (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Lawrence House
  - May 8, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - A Cyclone for a Cent (Box 11, Folder 15)
- The Mummers
  - May 21, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Greek Club
  - May 22, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Iphegenia at Aulis (Box 11, Folder 17)
      (see also: Department Clubs - Greek Club - Dramatics)
- Gillett House
  - Fall 1912 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - (unidentified) (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Morris House
  - Sept. 5, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Macbeth Burlesque (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Sock and Buskin
  - Nov. 23, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - The Policy of the House (Box 11, Folder 20)
- The Players
  - Mar. 15, 1913 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Pride and Prejudice (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Cap and Bells
  - Apr. 19, 1913 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Beau Brummel (Box 11, Folder 22)
- [Division of Dramatics]
  - [1913] (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Lost, Strayed or Stolen (Box 11, Folder 22)
- The Players
  - Nov. 22, 1913 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - A Scrap of Paper (Box 11, Folder 24)
- The Mummers
  - Dec. 13, 1913 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Cousin Kate (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Dewey - Clarke Players
  - Mar. 7, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Classy Vaudeville (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Baldwin House
  - Mar. 29, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - The Inventor (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Cap and Bells
  - Mar. 14, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - The Piper (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - Apr. 18, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - A Russian Honeymoon (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Sock and Buskin
  - May 16, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Mice and Men (Box 11, Folder 30)
- The Mummers
  - Nov. 14, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Major Barbara (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Cap and Bells
  - Dec. 12, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Monsieur Beaucaire (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Sock and Buskin
  - Mar. 6, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - A Rose o' Plymouth Town (Box 11, Folder 33)
- The Players
  - Apr. 24, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Trelawney of the Wells (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Cap and Bells
  - Nov. 20, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Cyrano de Bergerac (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Sock and Buskin
  - Dec. 18, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - The Shoes that Danced (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - The Rising of the Moon (Box 11)
- The Players
  - Mar. 4, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Lady Windermere's Fan (Box 12, Folder 1)
- The Mummers
  - May 29, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Master Skylark (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - Apr. 29, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - The Truth (Box 12, Folder 3)
- The Players
  - Dec. 9, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Chinese Lantern (Box 12, Folder 4)
- [for benefit of Dormitory Fund]
  - Jan. 17, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - The Bear (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Maker of Dreams (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Hat Shop (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Haven House
  - Oct. 13, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Mme. Beacharmarescha (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - How the Rhinoceros Got His Skin (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Two Hearts that Beat as One (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - Apr. 19, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Pygmalion and Galatea (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Sock and Buskin
  - Apr. 20, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Twig of Thorn (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Apr. 20, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Dorinda Dare (Box 12, Folder 9)
- [Theater Workshop]
  - Dec. 19, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Abraham and Isaac (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Nov. 21, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Behind a Watteau Picture (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Nov. 21, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Slave with Two Faces (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Theater Workshop
  - Dec. 18, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - On est Mieux ici Qu'en Face (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Apr. 22-23, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Pericles (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Dramatic Association
  - May 5, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Monsieur Beaucaire (Box 12, Folder 15)
- [Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi]
  - [1920-1921] (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Devil's Disciple (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 10, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - What Every Woman Knows (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Dec. 1, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Man of Destiny (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Dec. 1, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Tom Thumb the Great (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Theater Workshop
  - Jan. 20, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Gloriana (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Jan. 20, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Outcasts of Poker Flats (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Jan. 20, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Pierre and Jean (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Dramatic Association
  - Mar. 15, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - An Ideal Husband (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Dress Skit Contest
  - Apr. 16, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Alice through the Boudoir Glass (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Three Inches from the Floor (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - A Million A la Mode (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - A Corner in Spring (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Theater Workshop
  - May 5, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Avenues (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Dramatic Association
  - May 13, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - A Thousand Years Ago (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Theater Workshop
  - [1921] (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Duchess of Pavy (Box 12, Folder 26)
- (unidentified)
  - [1921] (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Three Pills in a Bottle (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Theater Workshop
  - Fall 1921 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Henry IV (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Oct. 22, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Hecuba (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Theater Workshop
  - Oct. 28, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Wandering Scholar (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 11, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - The Sabine Women (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Nov. 30, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Torches (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - May 3, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - If I Were King (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Theater Workshop
  - May 25, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Gamesters, Father and Son (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - The Immortal Sand (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - The Token (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - A Division of Despotism (Box 12, Folder 34)
- [Dramatic Association]
  - Oct. 22, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - The Romancers (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Will o' the Wisp (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - The Locked Chest (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Dramatic Association
  - Oct. 23, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Will o' the Wisp (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Theater Workshop
  - Oct. 25, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Scorpio (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Oct. 25, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - The Superfluous Soul (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Lima Beans (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Medea (Box 13, Folder 4)
- (unidentified)
  - Dec. 1, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Scarecrow (Box 13, Folder 5)
- [Theater Workshop]
  - Dec. 1922 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Everyman (Box 13, Folder 6)
- (unidentified)
  - 1923 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Never Be Pinned Down (Box 13, Folder 7)
- (unidentified)
  - 1923 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - The Second (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Shepherd's Play (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Theater Workshop
  - Jan. 1923 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Mrs. Adis (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - The Wrong Cue (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - The Eyes of the Panther (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - The Rat-Trap (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - May 9, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Makers of Song (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - The Gift of God (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Gloria Mundi (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Eight Plumbers and a Bootlegger (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Dramatic Association
  - Oct. 20, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Deirdre (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - The Knave of Hearts (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Beauty and the Jacobin (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Theater Workshop
  - Oct. 27, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - The Shepherd in the Distance (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Dramatic Association
  - Dec. 5, 1923 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Jeanne d'Arc (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Theater Workshop and Glee Club
  - Feb. 15, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Peter Crouch (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - A Triple Coincidence (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - The Shepherd in the Distance (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Feb. 28, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - The Wonderous Tales of Wen Chun Chin (Box 13, Folder 15)
- (unidentified)
  - 1923-1924 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Thy Kingdom Come (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Dramatic Association
  - Apr. 19, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - The Man Who Married a Dumb Wife (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Apr. 23, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - The Chinese Lantern (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - May 21-22, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Shakuntala (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Theater Workshop
  - Oct. 30, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Cobweb Kings (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - The Queen of Sheba (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Vote the New Moon (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Dramatic Association
  - Dec. 16, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - The Faithful (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Theater Workshop
  - Mar. 12, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - The Porcelain Cups (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Apr. 21, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Cross-currents (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Dramatic Association
  - 1924-1925 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - 'Op o' Me Thumb (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Teja (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Pearl of Dawn (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - May 16, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Misalliance (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Dramatic Association
  - May 20, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Grauch (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Patelin (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Spring 1925 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Plas and Mlisande (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Spring 1925 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - A Marriage of Convenience (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Theater Workshop
  - Oct. 13-14, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Great Catherine (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Nov. 18, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Compromise of the King of the Golden Isles (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Dramatic Association
  - Dec. 4-5, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Tragedy of a Man (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Spring 1926 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Ruy Blas (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Theater Workshop
  - May 1926 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - A Puppet Play (Box 13, Folder 33)
- [for benefit of Smith College Stage Fund]
  - Oct. 20, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - A Marriage of Convenience (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Dramatic Association
  - Dec. 1926 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Sappho and Phaon (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Theater Workshop
  - Feb. 10, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Noah (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Theater Workshop
  - Feb. 25, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Misgeneration (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Mock Beggar (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Bliss (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - The Sire de Maletroit's Door (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - May 1927 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - The Golden Door (Box 13, Folder 38)
- French Club
  - May 11, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - L'Anglais Tel Qu'on (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Le Parle (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Man Who Married a Dumb Wife (Box 13, Folder 39)
      (see Department Clubs - French Club 59.2 / Clubs / Fr.)
- (unidentified)
  - May 18, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Jael (Box 13, Folder 40)
- (unidentified)
  - 1927 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - A Dramatic Play (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 22, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Dear Brutus (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Theater Workshop
  - Nov. 25, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Extra-Curriculum (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Mar. 14, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Deirdre (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Mar. 14, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - The House of Ulna (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Dramatic Association
  - Apr.1928 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Beaux Stratagem (Box 14, Folder 5)
- [Theater Workshop]
  - Apr. 1928 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Twelfth Night (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Theater Workshop
  - Apr. 25-26, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - More Matter for a May Morning (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - May 24, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - A Merry Death (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Nov. 1-2, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Servant of Two Masters (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Dec. 15-16, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Miracle Play (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Jan. 19, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - On Trial (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Mar. 15, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Sir David Wears a Crown (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Apr. 23, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Bocaccio's "Untold Tale" (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Theater Workshop
  - May 22, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - King Lear's Wife (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Spring 1929 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Lilies of the Field (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Dramatic Association
  - May 27-28, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Caesar and Cleopatra (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Theater Workshop
  - 1929 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Pyentsa (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Nov. 6, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Flight of the Queen (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Dramatic Association
  - Dec. 13-14, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - The Chocolate Soldier (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Theater Workshop
  - Mar. 12, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - The Player Queen (Box 14, Folder 20)
- [for the benefit of the stage fund]
  - Apr. 26, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - And So On (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Theater Workshop
  - May 7, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Will o' the Wisp (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - May 7, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - The Widow's Veil (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Dramatic Association
  - Dec. 11-12, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Mary Rose (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - May 16, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Illuminati in Drame Libre (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - The Giant's Stair (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - A Marriage Proposal (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Theater Workshop
  - Dec. 1931 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Can You Hear Their Voices (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Dramatic Association
  - Dec. 4-5, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - The Treasure (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - Jan. 13, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Knight of the Burning Pestle (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Theater Workshop
  - Mar. 5, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Night Club (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Dramatic Association
  - Mar. 23, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - The Pretty Sabine Women (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Theater Workshop
  - May 17-18, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Pygmalion (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Dramatic Association
  - Oct. 29, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Pot of broth (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Will o' the Wisp (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - The Old Lady Shows her Medals (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Theater Workshop
  - Nov. 9-10, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Finished (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Dramatic Association
  - Dec. 13-14, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Berkeley Square (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Theater Workshop
  - Mar. 7, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - The Laughter of the Gods (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - Apr. 29, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - White Wings (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Theater Workshop
  - Nov. 14, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Behind a Watteau Picture (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Nov. 14, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - "L" (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Dramatic Association
  - Dec. 12-13, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Inheritors (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Dec. 15, 1933 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - The Enchanted Christmas Tree (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - The Wise Men (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - The Nursery maid of Heaven (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - 1933-1934 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - The Swan (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Theater Workshop
  - Mar. 7, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Concerning Spring (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Dramatic Association
  - Mar. 19-20, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - The Cradle Song (Box 14, Folder 43)
- (unidentified)
  - May 2-3, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - One for the Money (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 22, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Holiday (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - Apr. 18, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Cinderella (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Dramatic Association
  - May 9-10, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Autumn Crocus (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Dec. 5-6, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - The World We Live In (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Apr. 16-17, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - The Distaff Side (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Alpha-Phi Kappa Psi
  - May 14, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Toad of Toad Hall (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Dramatic Association
  - Dec. 15-16, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Maedchen in Uniform (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Theater Workshop
  - Feb. 1937 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Hay Fever (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Dramatic Association
  - Apr. 1937 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Dear Brutus (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Theater Workshop
  - Nov. 1, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - The Pretty Sabine Women (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 22, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Moor Born (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Theater Workshop
  - Feb. 1938 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Hotel Universe (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Dramatic Association
  - Mar. 17-18, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - First Lady (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Theater Workshop
  - Nov. 8, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Ardiane et Barbe-Bleue (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Dramatic Association
  - Nov. 17-18, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - The Infernal Machine (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Theater Workshop
  - Dec. 16, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Angel Wings (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Mar. 2, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Bargains in Cathay (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Sarah, Wife of Simon (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - On that Day (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Dramatic Association
  - Mar. 15-16, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Old Maid (Box 15, Folder 12)
- (unidentified)
  - Apr. 17, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Living Newspaper (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Theater Workshop
  - Nov. 2, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Fumed Oak (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Monday (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Theater of the Soul (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Everybody's Doing It (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Dec.7, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Vest Pocket Standby (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Foursome (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - The Artist (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Woman's Honor (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Workshop of the Arts
  - Dec. 13-14, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Electra (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Theater Workshop
  - Mar. 6, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - A Good Woman (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Over the Teacups (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Number Ten (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - A Kiss in Xanadu (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Dramatic Association
  - Mar. 14, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Call it a Day (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Theater Workshop
  - Apr. 17, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - The Cracked Teapot (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Cracked? Who Isn't? or, The City Slicker (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - The Romance of the Willow Pattern (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - This is Leap Year (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - May 8, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Pork Pie (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Gloria Mundi (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - The Purple Door-knob (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - May 16, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Sanctuary (Box 15, Folder 21)
- (unidentified)
  - Nov. 6, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Shadowy Waters (Box 15, Folder 22)
- [Dramatic Association]
  - Nov. 21, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Jonah and the Whale (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Theater Workshop
  - Dec. 5-6, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Recital (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Dec. 18, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Miracle Play (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Sleeping Beauty (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Of Time and the Blizzard (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Feb. 14, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Kind Lady (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Dramatic Association
  - Mar. 17-18, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - The Three Sisters (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Theater Workshop